Finding Aid for the Herschel Gower Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Reel to reel tape recordings
  - 15. Miscellaneous papers relating to the recordings including a term paper “The Ballad, the Archetype, and Rock Music” by John Muench (Box 13, Folder 15)